With this project, to get people's formation around forest -
- And be out with other people in the forest who are committed and want to learn more.
It gives an incredible amount of energy and joy.
So for me it has become a way to make my commitment more sustainable.
I have several examples here in Västerbotten where it is thanks to the commitment of individuals -
- That many forest areas remain.
That they were excluded from harvesting and maybe even today is a reserve.
My dream is well ..
... another forestry.
Where we do not have this calving use, but where all forests with high natural values receive long -term protection.
And that we use the forest in a different way than we do today.
It is a possible dream.